https://cheltenhampres.org.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Naunton Lane Evangelical Presbyterian Church uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.
We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Naunton Lane Evangelical Presbyterian Church may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from November 2014.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
your name
your email address
your telephone number
This information will only be collected with your knowledge and consent.
What we do with the information we gather
We use this information only in order to respond to any queries which you may submit through the site – it is not passed on to other parties. Should you ask for your data to be deleted once we have responded to your request, we will do so immediately. Otherwise, we will store your details for 6 months, in case we have any further need to contact you. After 6 months, your details will be removed from our system.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. This information is collected anonymously, and does not allow us to identify particular website visitors.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Have you got a question?
Fill in your details below and we'll get back to you as soon as we can.
Parking
There is ample parking in the adjacent Mead Road or other local roads that does not inconvenience local residents
23 Naunton Lane, Leckhampton, Cheltenham GL53 7BJ
